[MUSIC PLAYING]
Polycast 的观众朋友你们好  我是Rob
Hey there, Polycasters, Rob here.
欢迎回到  Ask Polymer
Welcome back to "Ask Polymer," the show where
你发送打上标签的问题  我们尽力来回答它们
you send in your hashtag questions, and we do our best to answer them.
好了  我们今天的第一个问题
OK, our first question today comes
来自 Marco  他说  国际化该怎么做
from Marco, who asks, what about internationalization?
我要引入外部的 JavaScript 框架
Do I have to use an external JavaScript framework,
还是说 Polymer 已经提供了某种解决方案
or is there some specific Polymer solution for that?
这是个好问题  一直有人问我这个
So that's a really good question and one that I get all the time.
现在我们有了一个帮助国际化的组件
Right now we have an element that will help with internationalization.
你可以点击这里查看
You can check it out over here.
它叫 i18n Message
It is called i18n Message.
由我们团队的一员  Eric Bidelman 写的
It was actually written by Eric Bidelman, one
已经用在了我们好几个网站上
of our team members, and used on a few of our sites.
从根本上讲  你在你的文本外面
And basically, the way it works is you take your text.
套一个 i18 Message 的标签就可以了
You wrap the i18 Message tag around your text.
然后给它一个消息的ID  通过这个 ID 来装载不同语言包的
And then you give it a message ID, which is synced up with a JSON file
JSON 文件进行同步
that loads different language packs.
这就是你现在可以使用的
So that is one solution that you can use
国际化解决方案
for internationalization today.
它并不是所有场景下都表现完美
It's not the bulletproof perfect solution for all scenarios,
但你可以从这里起步
but it is something to get you started.
我们最近还在开发一组叫做
And we're also currently working on a new set of elements
Carbon Elements 的组件
called Carbon Elements.
我们希望对于这些组件集
And our hope is that for those element sets,
依然会提供一些国际化的解决方案
we'll be rolling out some internationalization solutions as well.
所以谢谢你这个很棒的问题  Marco
So thank you for that awesome question, Marco.
好了  下一个问题来自 Sher
All right, our next question comes
他说  对于移动平台
from Sher, who asks, with the emphasis on mobile,
能否在3G网络下关闭波纹和其他特效
can ripple and other animations be turned off for 3G,
这能节省流量吗
and does that matter?
这个问题很棒
So that's a really cool question.
对于纸张波纹的特效
For something like the paper ripple animation,
你可以在组件中将它关闭
you actually can turn that off on your elements.
只需要在组件中加上一个 No Ink 属性
You just add a No Ink attribute to the element itself.
就可以禁用波纹效果
It will disable the ripple.
比如  你给纸张按钮加上这个属性  就不会有波纹了
So for instance, if you add that to Paper Button, it'll turn it off.
对于移动端来说  你应该做的是
Now for something like mobile, what you can do
用 iron-media-query
is you can use an iron media query
设置一个 handler 来检查屏幕尺寸
to set up a handler to check the screen size.
如果是小屏幕  你可以移除这个属性
And if it's a smaller screen, you can then remove that attribute.
如果是大屏幕  你可以将它加回来
Perhaps if it's a larger screen, you could add it back.
这样你就可以在桌面端有这个特性
So that way you could it have on desktop,
移动端没有  来保证性能的最大化
maybe take it away for mobile to get kind of maximum performance
there.
和往常一样  你希望测量性能
As always, you want to be measuring your performance.
如果什么东西确实是个阻碍
If something does seem like a bottleneck,
那么用相应的策略尝试移除它
then, yeah, use a strategy to try and remove it.
谢谢你提出了那么棒的问题  Sher
So thank you, Sher, for that really awesome question.
好了
All right.
下一个问题来自 Mark
Our next question comes from Mark,
他说  你如何为组件生成文档
who asks, how do you generate documentation for elements,
以及文档如何打包
and how do you document packages?
为了写一个组件的文档
So to document an element, what I typically do
我一般会用 seed-element 这个项目上手
is I start with this thing called the Seed Element Project.
你可以在 GitHub 上查看它
You can check that out over here on GitHub.
它会给你一个样板组件
And what that's going to do is give you a boilerplate
在 index 文件中的
element as well as, in the index file,
iron-component-page
this thing called Iron Component Pages.
iron-component-page 它会
And Iron Component Pages is going
读取你组件中的所有注释
to read all the comments in your element itself
来为你生成文档
and generate documentation for you.
你需要用到一些特殊的标记
Now there's special annotations that you have to use.
你可以查看这里的样式指南
And you can check out the style guide
来理解不同的标记
over here, which explains the different annotations.
但如果你刚开始写组件的时候
But if you basically work with that project
就使用了那个项目
as your starting point for your new elements,
你可以轻而易举地获得文档
then you're going to get documentation basically for free.
这是个很方便的工具
It's a pretty cool set up.
所以一定要去看看 seed-element 符不符合你的需要
So definitely check Seed Element and see if that meets your needs.
谢谢你 Mark 给出了这个很酷的问题
So thank you, Mark for sending in that really cool question.
好
OK.
下一个问题来自 Nicholas
Our next question comes from Nicholas,
他说  如何和CSS Mixins 一起使用媒体查询
who asks, how do you use CSS Mixins with media queries?
这是个很有趣的问题
So that is an interesting question.
现有样式填充系统的缺陷
Right now with the current limitations of the style
导致在媒体查询中你可以使用已有的变量
shimming system, in a media query you can consume variables.
但你不可以为自定义属性设置新的变量
However, you can't set new variables or custom properties.
所以你可以做的是  用 iron-media-query
So what you can do is use an Iron Media Query
组件来检查不同的屏幕尺寸
element to check the different screen sizes.
如果是小屏幕的话
And when it's a smaller screen size,
你可以调用 Polymer 的更新样式方法
you can call Polymer's Update Styles Method
真正传入新的属性
and actually pass in new properties that way.
事实上 GitHub 上有一条 issue
There's actually a GitHub issue which
就是在讨论这个问题  还提供了一个如何使用的样例
discusses this and shows an example of how you can work around it.
你可以去看一下
So you can check that out over here.
和 Mixins 一起使用的话
And for working with Mixins, what I can do
我可以做的是将 JS 组装到一起
is I can throw together a little JS bin,
然后加到一段简介上
and add that to the show description.
你同样可以在这里查看如何使用
So you can see how that works there as well.
谢谢 Nicholas 提出这个很棒的问题
So thank you, Nicholas, for sending in that awesome question.
我们最后一个问题来自 Jonathan
OK, our last question comes from Jonathan, who asks,
他说  你能不能简单地讲一讲
could you talk a little bit about the difference
paper-listbox 和 paper-menu 的区别
between paper-listbox versus paper-menu?
好  首先Jonathan  这远没有说到点子上
So, yeah, first of all, way to have an eagle eye, Jonathan.
我甚至完全不认为 paper-listbox 在我们的收录之中
And I don't even think paper-listbox is in our catalog yet.
它在GitHub上  你要承担尝试的风险
It is up on GitHub, so you're totally on the ball.
我理解的方式是 paper-listbox
The way that I understand things is paper-listbox
是一种选择组件
is kind of like the select element
你可以在上面添加多个属性
when you add a multi attribute to it.
你有很多个选项可以选择
So you get multiple things that you can choose from.
也许你想同时选择
Perhaps you want to even choose like one or two items
一个或两个选项
at the same time.
但是  paper-menu 更像是
However, the paper-menu is sort of more
传统的下拉式菜单
like a traditional drop-down menu.
这会是两者的区别
So that would be the difference between those two.
同样地  感谢你提出这个问题  Jonathan
Again, thank you so much for sending in that question, Jonathan.
今天就到这里
So that's it for today.
谢谢所有提出问题的观众
Thank you everyone who sent in those awesome questions.
如果你有什么问题
If you yourself have a question, you
在你的社交网络上
can ping us on a social network of your choosing
用#AskPolymer联系我们  或者在下面留下评论
at #AskPolymer, or leave it for us down below in the comments.
一如既往地感谢你们的观看  下期再见
As always, thank you so much for watching, and I'll see you next time.
[MUSIC PLAYING]